This is the final of the women's 50 metre freestyle.
On her 23rd birthday, Olivia Nel goes as one of the favourites for a medal in Lane
5. She's flanked by two Americans, Julia Dennis, quickest qualifier,
and Maxine Parker, one of the favourites for the gold.
While Dennis qualified with a 24.55 for this final, positions 2-8 were separated
by a quarter of a second in the semi-finals.
As it is Dennis who's leading the way, a massive underwater from her,
going nicely in Lane 1 is Ambler of Italy.
Now it's a chance for the field to chase down the two who are in front.
Nel is looking to come back here, but she's leaving it a little late.
Scotto Di Carlo looks good for a medal at the moment.
She's closing on Dennis, and Parker looks excellent.
She claims the gold splendidly.
Not quite so quick as the semi-final, but it's good enough for the gold medal.
Olivia Nel is on the podium.
She manages to get past the two Italians in the closing metres.
Maxine Parker takes the win ahead of Dennis by four hundredths of a second.
University of Virginia strikes again.
It's Parker.
She's finally got that individual gold.
One-two for USA, both comfortably sub 25 seconds.
Parker of Virginia wins gold ahead of Dennis.
Now to Louisville, and Olivia Nel on her birthday has bronze.